<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Welcome To Pelion</string>
    <string name="TextView">Almost all Pelion restaurants are traditional Greek taverns run by families. Such taverns are found in every village of this peninsula and many taverns are also located along some beaches. Makrinitsa, Portaria, Chania, Zagora, Agios Ioannis, Milina and Platanias, in particular, have many taverns. The most traditional dish in Pelion is spetsofai, a spicy dish with sausage and red sauce. Pelion restaurants are usually open from midday until midnight.</string>
    <string name="TextView2">Top 3 places to eat which recommended : </string>
    <string name="TextViewNature">The mountain is thickly forested, with both deciduous and perennial forests, mainly of beech, oak, maple and chestnut trees, with olive, apple, pear trees and plane tree groves surrounding places with water. Pelion is considered one of the most beautiful mountains in Greece and is a popular tourist attraction throughout the year: hiking trails and stone paths give access to springs, coves and numerous beaches, sandy or pebbly, set among lusciously green slopes. Pelion is an amply watered mountain with an abundance of springs, gorges, streams and rivulets; many streams are routed in carved-stone artificial beds to bring water to the villages and their thriving orchards. The higher elevations of the mountain receive enough snowfall so as to host skiing facilities that operate from Christmas to Easter.</string>
    <string name="TextViewMuseum"> The Folklore Museum of Makrinitsa in Pelion: Above the central square of Makrinitsa, one of the most picturesque villages of central Pelion, there is an interesting Folklore Museum housed in an elegant mansion with typical architecture of Pelion.</string>
    <string name="TextViewStay">Below you will find information about some of our suggested apartments for your holidays to Pelion</string>
    <string name="TextViewActivities">Being completely on its slopes, Pelion offers many opportunities for any kind of touristic activity. Anyone can try hiking, mountain biking or horse riding as there are many forest and countryside roads and paths useful for these activities and those who want to explore and enjoy places routes of great beauty with amazing view. These unique routes passing through fascinating forests on these unique paths in Pelion will be a real reward for you. Forthose fond of hard trekking there is panoramic view of the Pagasitikou gulf. On the other hand anyone preferring that surface trekking will enjoy mountain biking as they cycle on the shade of trees and they can always come across a spring to fill their bottle flask with fresh water. No doubt there are motorcycle opportunities too. The hills in Pelion offer adventure of any kind of motorbikes, cars and jeeps. There are hundreds of kilometers of rough roads in the mountains across the dense vegetation, full of high-rise trees of wild chestnuts and beech trees close to stone bridges over cold crystal-clear rivers. </string>
    <string name="TextViewlogo">Traditional villages, ski slopes, outdoor sports, heavenly beaches and dense forests… a place for all seasons</string>


</resources>